toyotafinancial.com 2010-12-04

# Toyota Financial Services: Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

|  | 

|   
---  
  
|   
---  

| 

Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

Effective as of May 20, 2009This page contains the online privacy policy and terms of use applicable to your usage of this website, toyotafinancial.com

Privacy Statement  
Normal Website Usage  
Collection and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information  
You May Request A Copy of Your Privacy Policy  
Your Choices  
Changes To Our Policy  
Accuracy of Your Information  
Confidentiality and Security  
Assistance for Victims of Identity Theft  
Terms of Use  
Questions, Comments or Complaints

 **Privacy Statement**

Toyota Motor Credit Corporation, Toyota Motor Insurance Services, Inc., and their subsidiaries (collectively, Toyota Financial Services, TFS, or we) respect your privacy and the confidential nature of the information that we gather during the course of our relationship with you. This Online Privacy Policy and Terms of Use  (“Online Policy”) describes Toyota Financial Services' policy regarding information received about you during visits to our website.  
  
 **Normal Website Usage**

You can visit Toyota Financial Services' website to read product, investment, and company information, or use some of our online tools (e.g., Which Vehicles Can I Afford? and Payment Estimator) without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. During these types of visits, we collect and store statistical information on an anonymous basis, such as the information about the time and length of your visit, the website you last visited, the pages you request, and the date and time of those requests. We may also collect and store the name of your Internet Service Provider.

We use cookies when you enter our website to help us gather this type of statistical information. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record keeping purposes so that we can track website and user activity. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you will find them at most websites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, if you do so, some parts of our website may not work properly for you.

We also use cookies to trigger certain online customer service surveys, which could be hosted on a site other than this site. These surveys are completely anonymous and optional. The information TFS and any outside survey company obtains from you if you choose to fill out these surveys is used only to improve your experience in visiting the TFS website.

 **Collection and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information**

There are instances where we request personally identifiable information to provide our website visitors a service or correspondence (e.g., promotions and mailed brochures). This information, such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, or type of request, is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the data and used to fulfill your request. If you are our customer, the information may also be shared as described below.

When you submit an online application to us or you are accessing your account online, we collect the following types of personally identifiable information about you:

  * Information that is required for you to register and log in to "your TFS Account", such as your account number, e-mail address, vehicle identification number, social security number, and zip code; and
  * Information we receive from you on applications for credit or other forms, such as your contact information, assets and income; and
  * Information we receive from you about your transactions with us, or affiliates (as permitted by law), or others such as account balances, payment history or account activity.

If you are a non-customer, TFS does not disclose personally identifiable information about you from your credit application or any credit reporting agencies, including your social security number, except as permitted by law. If you are a customer, TFS does not disclose personally identifiable information about you from your credit application or from credit reporting agencies, including your social security number, , except as permitted by law or any applicable TFS customer Privacy Policy.

If you are our customer, we may disclose all of the information that we collect on you and former customers, as described below.

To the extent permitted by law and in accordance with any applicable TFS customer Privacy Policy, the personally identifiable information we collect about you may be shared with our affiliates and nonaffiliated third parties as follows:

  * Financial products service providers, such as Toyota Motor Insurance Services, Inc. and Toyota Financial Savings Bank.
  * Non-financial companies engaged in the distribution, marketing, and sales of Lexus, Toyota and Scion automobiles, such as Toyota Motor Sales U.S.A., Inc., authorized Lexus, Toyota and Scion dealerships and other dealerships with which we have a business relationship, independent Lexus and Toyota dealerships' marketing associations, private Toyota distributors, nonaffiliated third parties calling us for information about your account with us, and nonaffiliated third parties who may sell your data in aggregate form for automotive marketing purposes.
  * Companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements.

We do not sell the collected data, regardless of whether you are a TFS customer.  
  
 **You May Request A Copy of Your TFS Customer Privacy Policy**

TFS continuously strives to comply with all applicable federal and state privacy laws. Some policies will vary by territory, based on the applicable laws of the region. If you are a finance or lease customer of TFS, you may request a copy of your customer Privacy Notice (if applicable) by calling us at 1-888-717-9248. TFS insurance customers may request a copy of their customer Privacy Policy (if applicable) by calling us at 1-800-255-8713.

 **Your Choices**

Finance and lease customers of Toyota Financial Services have certain privacy options that are provided pursuant to applicable federal and state privacy laws. To learn more about your privacy options, refer to the customer Privacy Policy mailed to you, or call us at 1-888-717-9248.

 **Changes To Our Policy**

As permitted by law, we may change this Online Policy and provide notice by posting a revised policy on this site. By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this Online Policy. Your continued use of this website after a revised Online Policy has been posted signifies your acceptance of the revised Online Policy.

 **Accuracy of Your Information**

You may contact us at 1-800-874-8822 regarding the accuracy, completeness and substance of the information collected about you while you are on this website.

 **Confidentiality and Security**

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you, including your social security number, to those employees and other persons hired by us who need to know the information to provide products and services to you and to otherwise service your account(s) with us. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.

If you choose to complete and submit our Online Credit Application, or to access your TFS Account, your personal information will be protected during transmission by an encryption process.

You can personally confirm the security of the site by viewing our certificate information. For Internet Explorer users, this can be found by clicking on "File" from your tool bar then "Properties" then "Certificates". It should indicate that the certificate is issued to my.toyotafinancial.com and issued by VeriSign Class 3 Secure Server. The certification provided on www.ToyotaFinancial.com has the highest level of security for our website.

For Firefox users, the certificates can be viewed by clicking on the lock icon in the bottom right corner of the browser.

 **Assistance for Victims of Identity Theft**

If you believe that your account has been subject to unauthorized access, please call us immediately at 1-800-874-8822. You may also contact your local law enforcement agency, and the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). You may speak with an FTC counselor by calling toll-free, 1-877-IDTheft (1-877-438-4338). Or, to enter information about your complaint to a FTC online database, sign on to www.consumer.gov/idtheft.

 **Terms of Use**

In addition to the terms of use contained on this page, supplemental terms of use may appear on specific pages of the website. This website contains information regarding Toyota Motor Credit Corporation, Toyota Motor Insurance Services, Inc., and Toyota Motor Sales, U.S.A., Inc. (jointly, "Toyota") and their products and promotional programs. Toyota Motor Credit Corporation, Toyota Motor Insurance Services, Inc., and their subsidiaries are collectively referred to as "Toyota Financial Services" or "TFS" throughout this website. Toyota Financial Services is a service mark of Toyota Motor Credit Corporation, Toyota Motor Insurance Services, Inc., and their subsidiaries.

We are not responsible for errors or negligent use of the services offered by this website, including input errors, negligent handling or sharing of passwords, and leaving a computer unattended while accessing the Online Credit Application or Manage Account section of the website.

While we make all reasonable efforts to ensure that all material on this website is correct, accuracy cannot be guaranteed. Balance or payment information that appears on My TFS Account assumes all payments posted to your account were valid postings made with good funds. This website may contain hypertext links to other websites that are completely independent of this website. We do not assume responsibility as to the accuracy, completeness, or authenticity of the information presented on any website accessed via such a link. A link to another entity's website should not be construed as endorsement by TFS of such entity's website, products, or services.

All of the content presented on this website is for information purposes only and in no way creates any fiduciary relationship between you and TFS; you should seek appropriate tax, financial, or legal advice when necessary. No content on this site constitutes an offer to buy or sell Toyota vehicles, nor does it constitute an offer of a direct loan or lease. All finance and insurance programs described in this website are available to qualified applicants only through Toyota Financial Services and participating Toyota dealers. All programs are subject to change or termination at any time. Final terms of purchase or lease are set by you and your Toyota dealer. The information contained on this website is protected by copyright and may not be reproduced without our written consent.

 **Questions, Comments or Complaints**

If you have questions, comments or complaints regarding this Online Policy, contact us at 1-888-717-9248.   
  
---  

Web Application Page
